<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Internet Security on Jongkonganteros</title>
    <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/internet-security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Internet Security on Jongkonganteros</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/internet-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is To Get Rid of That Annoying Facebook Page Linked To Your Account!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-get-rid-of-that-annoying-facebook-page-linked-to-your-account-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-get-rid-of-that-annoying-facebook-page-linked-to-your-account-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you tired of that annoying Facebook page that&amp;rsquo;s linked to your account? It&amp;rsquo;s a hassle to try to get rid of it, but don&amp;rsquo;t worry - it&amp;rsquo;s actually much easier than you think! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to quickly and easily remove a linked Facebook page from your account.
Steps to Remove Linked Facebook Page The first step is to log into your Facebook account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret to Anonymous Browsing: Discover How to Go Incognito on iPhone Google Now!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-anonymous-browsing-discover-how-to-go-incognito-on-iphone-google-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-anonymous-browsing-discover-how-to-go-incognito-on-iphone-google-now-/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the Secret to Anonymous Browsing Introduction Anonymous browsing is an important tool for protecting your privacy and security online. It allows you to browse the web without leaving a trace or record of your activity. In this article, we will explain what anonymous browsing is and how to go incognito on your iPhone Google Now.
Definition of Anonymous Browsing Anonymous browsing is a method of using the internet without revealing your identity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover the Secret to Staying Anonymous on Your iPad: Google Has the Answer!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/discover-the-secret-to-staying-anonymous-on-your-ipad-google-has-the-answer-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/discover-the-secret-to-staying-anonymous-on-your-ipad-google-has-the-answer-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction With the ever-increasing popularity of iPads, it is important to consider the security and privacy of your device. While the iPad has some built-in security features, it is not always enough to ensure that your data is safe. Fortunately, Google has developed a secure and anonymous solution to help you stay safe and secure on your iPad.
Overview of iPad&amp;rsquo;s Security Features The iPad is equipped with a range of security features to protect your data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
