<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Android on Jongkonganteros</title>
    <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/android/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Android on Jongkonganteros</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/android/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This One Trick Will Show You How to Turn Off Your Android Phone Even With a Broken Screen!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-one-trick-will-show-you-how-to-turn-off-your-android-phone-even-with-a-broken-screen-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-one-trick-will-show-you-how-to-turn-off-your-android-phone-even-with-a-broken-screen-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you dealing with a broken Android phone screen? If so, it can be difficult to power off the device and access its internal components. Fortunately, there is a trick that can help you turn off your Android phone even with a broken screen. In this blog post, we will discuss the steps to turn off your Android phone with a broken screen and the benefits of this trick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Verblüffe deine Freunde: So verwendest du dein Android Tablet als externen Monitor!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/verbl-ffe-deine-freunde-so-verwendest-du-dein-android-tablet-als-externen-monitor-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/verbl-ffe-deine-freunde-so-verwendest-du-dein-android-tablet-als-externen-monitor-/</guid>
      <description>Verblüffe deine Freunde: So verwendest du dein Android Tablet als externen Monitor! Du hast vielleicht schon einmal davon gehört, dass du dein Android Tablet als externen Monitor verwenden kannst. Aber du bist dir nicht ganz sicher, wie du das machen sollst? Keine Sorge, wir werden dir in diesem Blogpost genau erklären, wie du dein Android Tablet als externen Monitor verwenden kannst.
I. Einleitung Warum du einen externen Monitor benötigst Ein externer Monitor kann dir helfen, deine Produktivität zu steigern, indem du mehr Bildschirmfläche zur Verfügung hast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When We Tested This Android Auto Wireless Dongle!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-we-tested-this-android-auto-wireless-dongle-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-we-tested-this-android-auto-wireless-dongle-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you an Android user who wants to use their phone in the car? If so, you’ll be interested in our recent test of an Android Auto wireless dongle. In this blog post, we’ll discuss the background information, purpose of the test, testing process, results, and conclusion of the test.
Background Information Android Auto is a platform developed by Google that allows users to access their phone’s apps and services in the car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Let You Record Phone Calls on Your Android Phone - You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-let-you-record-phone-calls-on-your-android-phone-you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-let-you-record-phone-calls-on-your-android-phone-you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you ever wish you could record your phone calls? Whether you need to keep a record of important conversations or just want to save a funny exchange with a friend, recording your phone calls can be a great way to do it. Luckily, it&amp;rsquo;s easier than you think to record phone calls on your Android phone. Here&amp;rsquo;s a simple trick to get you started.
Overview of the Trick With this trick, you can easily record your phone calls on your Android device.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
