<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Emergency SOS on Jongkonganteros</title>
    <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/emergency-sos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Emergency SOS on Jongkonganteros</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/emergency-sos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Show You How to Instantly Disable Emergency SOS on Your iPhone 12 Mini!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-show-you-how-to-instantly-disable-emergency-sos-on-your-iphone-12-mini-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-show-you-how-to-instantly-disable-emergency-sos-on-your-iphone-12-mini-/</guid>
      <description>This Simple Trick Will Show You How to Instantly Disable Emergency SOS on Your iPhone 12 Mini! The iPhone 12 Mini is an incredibly powerful device, providing users with access to a wide range of features and capabilities. One of these features is Emergency SOS, which allows users to quickly and easily call for help in an emergency situation. However, if you don’t want to use this feature or find it to be too intrusive, you can easily disable it with just a few simple steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover the Simple Trick to Shut Off Emergency SOS on Your iPhone 13 Pro Max!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/discover-the-simple-trick-to-shut-off-emergency-sos-on-your-iphone-13-pro-max-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/discover-the-simple-trick-to-shut-off-emergency-sos-on-your-iphone-13-pro-max-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you have an iPhone 13 Pro Max? Are you worried about accidentally activating Emergency SOS? If so, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Fortunately, there is a simple trick to shut off Emergency SOS on your iPhone 13 Pro Max. Keep reading to learn how to do it!
What is Emergency SOS on iPhone 13 Pro Max? Emergency SOS is a feature on the iPhone 13 Pro Max that allows you to quickly call emergency services (such as 911) with a single tap.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
