<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DIY Projects on Jongkonganteros</title>
    <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/diy-projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DIY Projects on Jongkonganteros</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/diy-projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This 1 Trick Will Instantly Double Your iPhone 6s Plus Battery Life - You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-1-trick-will-instantly-double-your-iphone-6s-plus-battery-life-you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-1-trick-will-instantly-double-your-iphone-6s-plus-battery-life-you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction It can be incredibly frustrating when your iPhone 6s Plus battery dies in the middle of the day, leaving you without a way to communicate with the world. But what if we told you there was a simple trick that could instantly double your iPhone 6s Plus battery life? You won&amp;rsquo;t believe how easy it is!
Overview of the Trick This trick is incredibly simple: all you have to do is turn off the background app refresh feature on your iPhone 6s Plus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Easy Trick Will Have You Swapping Out Your iPhone 11 Pro Max Display in No Time!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-easy-trick-will-have-you-swapping-out-your-iphone-11-pro-max-display-in-no-time-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-easy-trick-will-have-you-swapping-out-your-iphone-11-pro-max-display-in-no-time-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to replace the display on your iPhone 11 Pro Max, you&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place! In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the entire process, step-by-step. We&amp;rsquo;ll also provide some helpful tips to ensure a successful display replacement.
Overview of the iPhone 11 Pro Max The iPhone 11 Pro Max is the latest and greatest in Apple&amp;rsquo;s line of smartphones. It features a 6.5-inch OLED display, a powerful A13 Bionic processor, and a triple-camera array that can take stunning photos and videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is To Replace Your iPhone 12 Mini&#39;s Original Battery!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-replace-your-iphone-12-mini-s-original-battery-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-replace-your-iphone-12-mini-s-original-battery-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you the proud owner of an iPhone 12 Mini? You know that these devices are designed to last, but even the most reliable devices will eventually need to be serviced or repaired. One of the most common repairs is replacing the battery. Fortunately, replacing the battery on an iPhone 12 Mini is a simple process that anyone can do.
Overview of iPhone 12 Mini and its Battery The iPhone 12 Mini is a powerful and reliable device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astonishing Trick: Unfreeze Your iPhone XR Without Even Touching the Power Button!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/astonishing-trick-unfreeze-your-iphone-xr-without-even-touching-the-power-button-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/astonishing-trick-unfreeze-your-iphone-xr-without-even-touching-the-power-button-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Unfreezing Your iPhone XR Without Even Touching the Power Button The iPhone XR is one of the most popular and powerful smartphones on the market. It has a sleek design, powerful processor, and a plethora of features that make it a great device. Unfortunately, the iPhone XR can sometimes freeze or become unresponsive. This can be incredibly frustrating, as it can take a long time to get the device back up and running.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
