<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>iPhone Tricks on Jongkonganteros</title>
    <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/iphone-tricks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in iPhone Tricks on Jongkonganteros</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/iphone-tricks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This iPhone Trick Will Have You Recording Videos With Music Playing Instantly!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-iphone-trick-will-have-you-recording-videos-with-music-playing-instantly-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-iphone-trick-will-have-you-recording-videos-with-music-playing-instantly-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you want to record videos with music playing in the background? It&amp;rsquo;s easier than you think! With this simple iPhone trick, you can record videos with music playing instantly.
Overview of the iPhone Trick This iPhone trick is designed to make it easy to record videos with music playing in the background. All you need is an external speaker, your iPhone, and a few simple steps.
Benefits of the Trick The benefit of this trick is that it allows you to record videos with music playing in the background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shocking Trick to Instantly Turn Off SOS on iPhone 13 - You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens Next!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/shocking-trick-to-instantly-turn-off-sos-on-iphone-13-you-won-t-believe-what-happens-next-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/shocking-trick-to-instantly-turn-off-sos-on-iphone-13-you-won-t-believe-what-happens-next-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you having trouble with the SOS feature on your iPhone 13? Do you want to know how to instantly turn it off? If so, you&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explain how to instantly turn off SOS on iPhone 13, as well as the benefits of doing so.
Background of the Issue The SOS feature on the iPhone 13 is designed to help you in an emergency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unbelievable Trick: Record Audio on Your iPhone While Playing Music Simultaneously!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unbelievable-trick-record-audio-on-your-iphone-while-playing-music-simultaneously-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unbelievable-trick-record-audio-on-your-iphone-while-playing-music-simultaneously-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wanted to record audio on your iPhone while playing music simultaneously? It&amp;rsquo;s an incredible trick that can be used to record podcasts, interviews, and more. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at the benefits of recording audio on your iPhone while playing music simultaneously, as well as a step-by-step guide to help you get started.
Overview of the Trick The trick to recording audio on your iPhone while playing music simultaneously is to use a recording app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Trick: Discover How to Locate Your Lost iPhone Without an iCloud Account!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/amazing-trick-discover-how-to-locate-your-lost-iphone-without-an-icloud-account-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/amazing-trick-discover-how-to-locate-your-lost-iphone-without-an-icloud-account-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever misplaced your iPhone and thought to yourself, “How can I find my lost iPhone without an iCloud account?” If so, you’re in luck. With the right tools, you can easily locate your lost iPhone without an iCloud account.
How to Find a Lost iPhone Without an iCloud Account The first step to finding your lost iPhone without an iCloud account is to download a tracking app. There are many tracking apps available, such as Find My iPhone and Prey Anti-Theft, that can help you locate your device.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
