<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DIY on Jongkonganteros</title>
    <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/diy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DIY on Jongkonganteros</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/diy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Surprising Trick: Learn How to Factory Reset Your iPhone XR Manually in Just 3 Steps!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/surprising-trick-learn-how-to-factory-reset-your-iphone-xr-manually-in-just-3-steps-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/surprising-trick-learn-how-to-factory-reset-your-iphone-xr-manually-in-just-3-steps-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a way to factory reset your iPhone XR manually? If so, you have come to the right place! In this blog post, we will provide a step-by-step guide on how to factory reset your iPhone XR manually.
Overview of the iPhone XR The iPhone XR is a popular smartphone from Apple. It features a 6.1-inch LCD display, an A12 Bionic processor, and a 12MP rear camera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jetzt Akku deines iPhone SE 2016 ganz einfach selbst austauschen!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/jetzt-akku-deines-iphone-se-2016-ganz-einfach-selbst-austauschen-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/jetzt-akku-deines-iphone-se-2016-ganz-einfach-selbst-austauschen-/</guid>
      <description>Jetzt Akku deines iPhone SE 2016 ganz einfach selbst austauschen! I. Einleitung Der Akku deines iPhone SE 2016 ist defekt? Kein Problem! Mit ein wenig technischem Geschick und den richtigen Werkzeugen kannst du deinen Akku ganz einfach selbst austauschen. In diesem Blogpost erfährst du, warum es sinnvoll ist, deinen Akku selbst zu ersetzen, was du dafür benötigst und wie du den Austausch durchführen kannst.
A. Warum du deinen Akku selbst austauschen solltest Es gibt viele Gründe, warum du deinen Akku selbst austauschen solltest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surprise! Here&#39;s the Quick Trick to Instantly Reset Your iPhone XR Battery!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/surprise-here-s-the-quick-trick-to-instantly-reset-your-iphone-xr-battery-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/surprise-here-s-the-quick-trick-to-instantly-reset-your-iphone-xr-battery-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you an iPhone XR user looking for a quick and easy way to reset your battery? Well, you’ve come to the right place! In this blog post, we’ll be discussing a quick trick to instantly reset your iPhone XR battery.
What is an iPhone XR? The iPhone XR is a smartphone released by Apple in 2018. It features a 6.1-inch LCD display, a single-lens rear camera, and an A12 Bionic processor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
