<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutorials on Jongkonganteros</title>
    <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/tutorials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tutorials on Jongkonganteros</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This 1 Simple Trick Will Reset Your iPhone 11 Pro Without a Passcode - You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens Next!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-1-simple-trick-will-reset-your-iphone-11-pro-without-a-passcode-you-won-t-believe-what-happens-next-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-1-simple-trick-will-reset-your-iphone-11-pro-without-a-passcode-you-won-t-believe-what-happens-next-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a way to reset your iPhone 11 Pro without a passcode? If so, then you&amp;rsquo;re in luck! This article will show you a simple trick that will help you reset your iPhone 11 Pro without a passcode. We&amp;rsquo;ll also provide some additional tips to help you get the most out of your device.
Benefits of the Trick Resetting your iPhone 11 Pro without a passcode can be a great way to start fresh with your device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astonishingly Easy: Learn How to Record Your iPhone 8 Plus Screen with Music in Just 5 Steps!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/astonishingly-easy-learn-how-to-record-your-iphone-8-plus-screen-with-music-in-just-5-steps-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/astonishingly-easy-learn-how-to-record-your-iphone-8-plus-screen-with-music-in-just-5-steps-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you want to record your iPhone 8 Plus screen with music? It’s easier than you think! With the right tools and a few steps, you can easily record your iPhone 8 Plus screen with music. In this blog post, we’ll explain what recording your iPhone 8 Plus screen with music is and the benefits of doing so. We’ll also provide a step-by-step guide to recording your iPhone 8 Plus screen with music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret: Discover How to Take Screenshots on Your Android Tablet 4.0.4!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-discover-how-to-take-screenshots-on-your-android-tablet-4-0-4-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-discover-how-to-take-screenshots-on-your-android-tablet-4-0-4-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you an Android tablet user? Do you want to know how to take screenshots on your Android tablet 4.0.4? If so, you’ve come to the right place! In this blog post, we’ll explain what screenshots are, why they’re useful, and provide a step-by-step guide to taking screenshots on an Android tablet 4.0.4.
What is a Screenshot? A screenshot is an image of what’s currently being displayed on your screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Trick! Learn How to Record Your iPhone 8 Plus Screen with Music Instantly!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/amazing-trick-learn-how-to-record-your-iphone-8-plus-screen-with-music-instantly-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/amazing-trick-learn-how-to-record-your-iphone-8-plus-screen-with-music-instantly-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you want to learn how to record your iPhone 8 Plus screen with music instantly? If so, then you’ve come to the right place! In this blog post, we’ll explain the benefits of recording your iPhone 8 Plus screen and provide a step-by-step guide on how to do it. Let’s get started!
Benefits of Recording Your iPhone 8 Plus Screen Recording your iPhone 8 Plus screen can be incredibly useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unbelievable Trick: Discover How to Restart Your iPhone XR in Seconds!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unbelievable-trick-discover-how-to-restart-your-iphone-xr-in-seconds-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unbelievable-trick-discover-how-to-restart-your-iphone-xr-in-seconds-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a quick and easy way to restart your iPhone XR? If so, you&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll be discussing the incredible trick to restart your iPhone XR in just seconds.
Definition of iPhone XR The iPhone XR is a smartphone designed and marketed by Apple Inc. It was released in September 2018 and is the twelfth generation of the iPhone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surprise! You Can Hard Reset Your iPhone XR with Just a Few Buttons - Here&#39;s How!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/surprise-you-can-hard-reset-your-iphone-xr-with-just-a-few-buttons-here-s-how-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/surprise-you-can-hard-reset-your-iphone-xr-with-just-a-few-buttons-here-s-how-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever felt like you need to hit the reset button on your iPhone XR? You’re in luck! With just a few simple steps, you can hard reset your iPhone XR and get it back to its factory settings. Let’s take a look at what a hard reset is, the benefits of doing one, and how to do it.
What is a Hard Reset? A hard reset is a process of restoring a device to its original factory settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unbelievable Trick: Easily Restart Your iPhone XR with Just a Few Buttons!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unbelievable-trick-easily-restart-your-iphone-xr-with-just-a-few-buttons-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unbelievable-trick-easily-restart-your-iphone-xr-with-just-a-few-buttons-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Restarting Your iPhone XR The iPhone XR is a popular smartphone that offers a great combination of features and performance. While it&amp;rsquo;s a reliable device, it can occasionally run into issues that require a restart. Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s an easy and quick way to restart your iPhone XR with just a few buttons. Read on to find out how!
What is an iPhone XR? The iPhone XR is a flagship device from Apple that was released in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One Trick Will Instantly Reset Your iPhone 7 Plus - You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is With iTunes!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-one-trick-will-instantly-reset-your-iphone-7-plus-you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-with-itunes-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-one-trick-will-instantly-reset-your-iphone-7-plus-you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-with-itunes-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wanted to reset your iPhone 7 Plus but didn&amp;rsquo;t know how? We have the perfect trick for you! With iTunes, you can reset your iPhone 7 Plus in just a few simple steps.
What is the trick? The trick is to reset your iPhone 7 Plus with iTunes. This is an incredibly easy process that will help you reset your phone quickly and efficiently.
Benefits of the Trick The main benefit of this trick is that it will help you quickly reset your iPhone 7 Plus without having to go through a lengthy process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incredible Trick: How to Take Full-Page Screenshots on Your iPhone 11 - You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/incredible-trick-how-to-take-full-page-screenshots-on-your-iphone-11-you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/incredible-trick-how-to-take-full-page-screenshots-on-your-iphone-11-you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Taking Full-Page Screenshots on Your iPhone 11 Do you ever wish you could take a screenshot of an entire webpage on your iPhone 11? Well, you can! Taking full-page screenshots on your iPhone 11 is surprisingly easy and can be done in a matter of minutes.
What is a Full-Page Screenshot? A full-page screenshot is a single image that captures an entire webpage. This is different from the typical screenshot you take on your iPhone, which only captures a portion of the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incredible Trick: Easily Disable Call Forwarding on Your iPhone 8 Plus in Just 3 Steps!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/incredible-trick-easily-disable-call-forwarding-on-your-iphone-8-plus-in-just-3-steps-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/incredible-trick-easily-disable-call-forwarding-on-your-iphone-8-plus-in-just-3-steps-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you an iPhone 8 Plus user looking for an easy way to disable call forwarding? Then you’ve come to the right place! In this article, we’ll walk you through the simple steps needed to disable call forwarding on your iPhone 8 Plus in just three easy steps.
What is Call Forwarding? Call forwarding is a feature that allows you to forward incoming calls to another phone number. This can be helpful if you need to forward your calls to another phone, such as a work phone or a home phone.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
