<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech Tips on Jongkonganteros</title>
    <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/tech-tips/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech Tips on Jongkonganteros</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/tech-tips/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Help You Backup Your iPhone to an External Hard Drive on Windows - You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-help-you-backup-your-iphone-to-an-external-hard-drive-on-windows-you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-help-you-backup-your-iphone-to-an-external-hard-drive-on-windows-you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you want to back up your iPhone to an external hard drive on Windows? It&amp;rsquo;s easier than you think! This simple trick can help you quickly and easily back up your iPhone data to an external hard drive. Read on to learn more about the process and how to get started.
Definition of Backing Up an iPhone Backing up an iPhone is the process of creating a copy of your iPhone data, such as photos, contacts, messages, and more, and storing it on another device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This 1 Trick Will Change the Way You Take Videos on Your iPhone - Keep Music Playing the Whole Time!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-1-trick-will-change-the-way-you-take-videos-on-your-iphone-keep-music-playing-the-whole-time-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-1-trick-will-change-the-way-you-take-videos-on-your-iphone-keep-music-playing-the-whole-time-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you an iPhone user who loves taking videos and listening to music? If so, you&amp;rsquo;ll be excited to hear about this one trick that will revolutionize the way you take videos on your iPhone. This trick will allow you to keep music playing the whole time you take videos, resulting in improved video quality and increased enjoyment of music.
Background Information With the rise of social media platforms like Instagram and TikTok, taking videos on your phone has become increasingly popular.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is to Make Your iPhone 8 Plus Screen Rotate!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-make-your-iphone-8-plus-screen-rotate-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-make-your-iphone-8-plus-screen-rotate-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for an easy way to make your iPhone 8 Plus screen rotate? If so, you’ve come to the right place! In this blog post, we’ll provide a step-by-step guide on how to enable the screen rotation feature on the iPhone 8 Plus and how to rotate the screen manually or with the help of a third-party app.
Overview of the iPhone 8 Plus The iPhone 8 Plus is one of the most popular smartphones on the market today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One Trick Will Make Adding Music to Your iPhone 13 Videos a Breeze!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-one-trick-will-make-adding-music-to-your-iphone-13-videos-a-breeze-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-one-trick-will-make-adding-music-to-your-iphone-13-videos-a-breeze-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Adding music to your iPhone 13 videos can be a hassle. However, with the right trick, you can make the process a breeze! This guide will walk you through the steps needed to add music to your iPhone 13 videos quickly and easily.
Step-by-Step Guide The first step is to download the necessary software. This software will allow you to connect your iPhone to your computer and drag and drop the music into the video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Unlock Your Samsung Android Phone Instantly - No Factory Reset Needed!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-unlock-your-samsung-android-phone-instantly-no-factory-reset-needed-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-unlock-your-samsung-android-phone-instantly-no-factory-reset-needed-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever been locked out of your Samsung Android phone and been unable to access it? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there is an easy solution to this problem. Now you can unlock your Samsung Android phone instantly, without having to perform a factory reset. This simple trick will help you gain access to your phone in no time.
Overview of the Trick The trick involves downloading an unlocking app to your phone and activating it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unbelievable: Easily Reset Your iPhone 11 Pro Max Without a Passcode - Here&#39;s How!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unbelievable-easily-reset-your-iphone-11-pro-max-without-a-passcode-here-s-how-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unbelievable-easily-reset-your-iphone-11-pro-max-without-a-passcode-here-s-how-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a way to easily reset your iPhone 11 Pro Max without a passcode? If so, this post is for you! In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the overview of the iPhone 11 Pro Max, the reasons why you may need to reset it without a passcode, and the steps you need to take to reset your iPhone 11 Pro Max without a passcode.
Overview of iPhone 11 Pro Max The iPhone 11 Pro Max is the newest and most powerful iPhone model to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surprising Trick: Easily Backup Your iPhone on Windows PC Without iTunes!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/surprising-trick-easily-backup-your-iphone-on-windows-pc-without-itunes-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/surprising-trick-easily-backup-your-iphone-on-windows-pc-without-itunes-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you a Windows user who is looking for a way to easily backup your iPhone data without having to use iTunes? Don’t worry, we’ve got you covered! In this blog post, we’ll show you a simple trick to quickly and easily backup your iPhone data on a Windows PC without having to use iTunes.
Step-by-Step Guide on How to Backup Your iPhone Without iTunes Download and install the free EaseUS MobiMover software on your Windows PC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Help You Reset Your iPhone 11 Pro Max When It&#39;s Frozen!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-help-you-reset-your-iphone-11-pro-max-when-it-s-frozen-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-help-you-reset-your-iphone-11-pro-max-when-it-s-frozen-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you having trouble with your iPhone 11 Pro Max? Is it frozen and unresponsive? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, this simple trick will help you reset your iPhone 11 Pro Max when it&amp;rsquo;s frozen!
Overview of iPhone 11 Pro Max The iPhone 11 Pro Max is the latest and most powerful iPhone from Apple. It features an impressive A13 Bionic chip, a 6.5-inch Super Retina XDR display, and a triple-camera system. It also has an IP68 dust and water resistance rating, making it one of the most durable iPhones ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unbelievable! This One Trick Will Have You Factory Resetting Your iPhone XS Max in Seconds with iTunes!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unbelievable-this-one-trick-will-have-you-factory-resetting-your-iphone-xs-max-in-seconds-with-itunes-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unbelievable-this-one-trick-will-have-you-factory-resetting-your-iphone-xs-max-in-seconds-with-itunes-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a fast and easy way to factory reset your iPhone XS Max? With this one trick, you can have your phone reset in seconds with the help of iTunes!
Definition of Factory Resetting and its Importance A factory reset is a process that erases all the data and settings on your device and restores it to its factory settings. It is important to do this if you are selling your device or if you are experiencing any issues with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This 1 Trick Will Help You Instantly Reboot Your iPhone 14 Pro Max When It Freezes!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-1-trick-will-help-you-instantly-reboot-your-iphone-14-pro-max-when-it-freezes-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-1-trick-will-help-you-instantly-reboot-your-iphone-14-pro-max-when-it-freezes-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you frustrated when your iPhone 14 Pro Max freezes? It&amp;rsquo;s a common problem and it can be really annoying. But don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s a trick that can help you reboot your phone quickly and easily! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the iPhone 14 Pro Max and the problem of freezing, and then we&amp;rsquo;ll explain the trick to instantly reboot your phone.
Overview of the iPhone 14 Pro Max The iPhone 14 Pro Max is the latest and greatest model from Apple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unbelievable: This Simple Trick Will Help You Find Your Lost iPhone Using Your Apple Watch!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unbelievable-this-simple-trick-will-help-you-find-your-lost-iphone-using-your-apple-watch-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unbelievable-this-simple-trick-will-help-you-find-your-lost-iphone-using-your-apple-watch-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever lost your iPhone and felt completely helpless? Well, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry anymore because there is a simple trick that can help you find your lost iPhone using your Apple Watch! With this trick, you can easily locate your iPhone and save yourself the headache of searching for it.
Steps to Find Your Lost iPhone with Your Apple Watch The first step is to make sure that your Apple Watch and iPhone are connected via Bluetooth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Get Stuck in SOS Mode: Here&#39;s How to Easily Turn it Off on iPhone 12!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/don-t-get-stuck-in-sos-mode-here-s-how-to-easily-turn-it-off-on-iphone-12-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/don-t-get-stuck-in-sos-mode-here-s-how-to-easily-turn-it-off-on-iphone-12-/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t Get Stuck in SOS Mode: Here&amp;rsquo;s How to Easily Turn it Off on iPhone 12! The iPhone 12 has many features that make it a great phone. One of those features is the Emergency SOS mode, which is designed to provide users with quick access to emergency services. Unfortunately, this feature can be a bit of a nuisance if you don&amp;rsquo;t know how to turn it off.
Introduction Emergency SOS mode, or SOS mode, is a feature on the iPhone 12 that allows users to quickly access emergency services by pressing the side button five times in quick succession.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Have Your Android 11 Phone Reset in Seconds!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-have-your-android-11-phone-reset-in-seconds-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-have-your-android-11-phone-reset-in-seconds-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Android 11 is the latest version of the Android operating system, released in September 2020. It comes with a range of new features, including improved privacy and security, better control of notifications, and support for 5G networks. With all these new features, it can be difficult to keep track of everything. That&amp;rsquo;s why it&amp;rsquo;s important to know how to reset your Android 11 phone quickly and easily.
Overview of the Simple Trick The good news is that resetting your Android 11 phone is actually quite simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Unlock Your iPhone SE Without Needing iTunes or a Computer!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-unlock-your-iphone-se-without-needing-itunes-or-a-computer-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-unlock-your-iphone-se-without-needing-itunes-or-a-computer-/</guid>
      <description>Unlock Your iPhone SE Without iTunes or a Computer Introduction Are you looking for a way to unlock your iPhone SE without iTunes or a computer? If so, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck! We have a simple trick that can help you unlock your iPhone SE without the need for iTunes or a computer.
Background Information The iPhone SE was released in March 2016 and was the successor to the iPhone 5S. It was the last iPhone to feature a 4-inch display and was the last iPhone to be released with a physical home button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret to Fixing Your Frozen iPhone XR in Just 5 Minutes!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-fixing-your-frozen-iphone-xr-in-just-5-minutes-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-to-fixing-your-frozen-iphone-xr-in-just-5-minutes-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you having trouble with your iPhone XR? If it&amp;rsquo;s frozen and won&amp;rsquo;t respond to your commands, don&amp;rsquo;t worry. You can fix it in just five minutes! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the steps to get your device back up and running in no time.
Definition of an iPhone XR The iPhone XR is a smartphone designed by Apple Inc. It was released in 2018 and is the successor to the iPhone X.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
