<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech Troubleshooting on Jongkonganteros</title>
    <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/tech-troubleshooting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech Troubleshooting on Jongkonganteros</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/tech-troubleshooting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Solve the Mystery: How to Get Your iPhone to Share Location Again!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/solve-the-mystery-how-to-get-your-iphone-to-share-location-again-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/solve-the-mystery-how-to-get-your-iphone-to-share-location-again-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever tried to share your location with a friend or family member and found that it wasn&amp;rsquo;t working? If so, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Many iPhone users have experienced this issue, but luckily, there are a few troubleshooting steps you can take to get your iPhone to share location again.
Troubleshooting Steps Check iPhone Privacy Settings: First, check your iPhone&amp;rsquo;s privacy settings to make sure that location sharing is enabled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is To Fix Your iPhone 14 Pro Max When It Freezes - Here&#39;s How!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-fix-your-iphone-14-pro-max-when-it-freezes-here-s-how-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-fix-your-iphone-14-pro-max-when-it-freezes-here-s-how-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you having trouble with your iPhone 14 Pro Max freezing up? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone! Many people have been experiencing this issue and it&amp;rsquo;s not as difficult to fix as you may think. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the steps you can take to quickly and easily fix your iPhone 14 Pro Max when it freezes.
Overview of the Problem The iPhone 14 Pro Max is one of the most popular and powerful smartphones on the market today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Struggling to Sign In to Find My iPhone? Here&#39;s the Solution You Need!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/struggling-to-sign-in-to-find-my-iphone-here-s-the-solution-you-need-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/struggling-to-sign-in-to-find-my-iphone-here-s-the-solution-you-need-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Find My iPhone Have you ever been frustrated trying to sign in to your Find My iPhone app? It can be a challenge, but don&amp;rsquo;t worry, we have the solution you need!
Find My iPhone is an app that helps you locate your lost or stolen Apple device. It works by using the GPS and cellular data of your device to pinpoint its location. It also lets you remotely lock or erase the data on your device if it&amp;rsquo;s been stolen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secret: Discover How to Reset Your iPhone XS Max to Factory Settings Without a Passcode!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-discover-how-to-reset-your-iphone-xs-max-to-factory-settings-without-a-passcode-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/unlock-the-secret-discover-how-to-reset-your-iphone-xs-max-to-factory-settings-without-a-passcode-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a way to reset your iPhone XS Max to its factory settings without a passcode? If so, you’ve come to the right place. In this blog post, we’ll walk you through the steps to reset your iPhone XS Max to its factory settings without a passcode.
Overview of iPhone XS Max The iPhone XS Max is Apple’s flagship device, released in 2018. It has a 6.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
