<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows 10 on Jongkonganteros</title>
    <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/windows-10/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Windows 10 on Jongkonganteros</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jongkonganteros.github.io/tags/windows-10/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Totally Transform Your iPhone With This One Easy Trick: How to Back Up to External Hard Drive on Windows 10!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/totally-transform-your-iphone-with-this-one-easy-trick-how-to-back-up-to-external-hard-drive-on-windows-10-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/totally-transform-your-iphone-with-this-one-easy-trick-how-to-back-up-to-external-hard-drive-on-windows-10-/</guid>
      <description>Totally Transform Your iPhone With This One Easy Trick: How to Back Up to External Hard Drive on Windows 10! Are you looking for an easy way to back up your iPhone&amp;rsquo;s data and keep it safe? Look no further! This guide will show you how to back up your iPhone to an external hard drive on Windows 10.
Introduction A hard drive is a storage device that stores digital information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is to Copy Your iPhone Backup to an External Hard Drive in Windows 10!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-copy-your-iphone-backup-to-an-external-hard-drive-in-windows-10-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-copy-your-iphone-backup-to-an-external-hard-drive-in-windows-10-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you need to copy your iPhone backup to an external hard drive in Windows 10? We’ve got you covered! In this blog post, we’ll explain what an iPhone backup is, the benefits of copying an iPhone backup to an external hard drive, and the steps to copy an iPhone backup to an external hard drive in Windows 10.
Definition of an iPhone Backup An iPhone backup is a snapshot of your iPhone’s data that is stored on your computer or an external hard drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surprise Trick: Easily Move Your iPhone Backup to an External Hard Drive in Windows 10!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/surprise-trick-easily-move-your-iphone-backup-to-an-external-hard-drive-in-windows-10-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/surprise-trick-easily-move-your-iphone-backup-to-an-external-hard-drive-in-windows-10-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Moving Your iPhone Backup to an External Hard Drive An external hard drive is a storage device that is not part of the computer’s internal components. It is a separate device that can be connected to the computer through a USB port. An external hard drive is a great way to store large amounts of data and can be used to back up important files.
One of the most important files on your iPhone is your backup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easily Backup Your iPhone Photos and Videos in Just 3 Simple Steps - Windows 10 Edition!</title>
      <link>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/easily-backup-your-iphone-photos-and-videos-in-just-3-simple-steps-windows-10-edition-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jongkonganteros.github.io/posts/easily-backup-your-iphone-photos-and-videos-in-just-3-simple-steps-windows-10-edition-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Backing Up Your iPhone Photos and Videos Backing up your photos and videos from your iPhone is a great way to ensure that your memories are safe and secure. It also allows you to free up space on your device by transferring photos and videos to your computer. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll be discussing how to easily backup your iPhone photos and videos in just three simple steps, using Windows 10.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
